(Leonard:)-It's obviously a typo.
-Perhaps.
Or perhaps this restaurant's now
a front for organized crime.
(Sheldon:)For all we know, the mobster sauce...
(Sheldon:)...contains actual chunks
of deceased mobsters.
(Raj:)No, no, no. I think it just means
it's the kind of sauce that mobsters like.
(Howard:)It doesn't mean any of that.
It's a typo.
(Leonard:)-You know what? Let's just get a pizza.
-Good idea. We'll go to Corleone's.
(Howard:)Sure, no mobsters there.
(Sheldon:)You know, the more I think about it...
(Sheldon:)...the mobster sauce couldn't
possibly contain chunks of mobster.
LEONARD: And why is that?
-It was listed under "seafood."
(Leonard:)What if they were mobsters
who slept with the fishes?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, are we having
a serious conversation or not?
LEONARD:
What the--?
(Sheldon:)-The TV is gone.
-So are our laptops.
(Sheldon:)Oh, God. Oh, God.
(Raj:)Oh, God!
(Sheldon:)It's all right.
(Sheldon:)They didn't take my comic books.